export const chapter = "Chapter - 11: Prepositions ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "What type of prepositions are 'at,' 'by,' 'for,' and 'from'?",
          optionA: "A. Simple prepositions",
          optionB: "B. Compound prepositions",
          optionC: "C. Complex prepositions",
          correctAnswer: "A. Simple prepositions",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'This gift has come from my uncle, please keep it on the table,' what are the prepositions used?",
          optionA: "A. from, on",
          optionB: "B. by, for",
          optionC: "C. with, within",
          correctAnswer: "A. from, on",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of a compound preposition?",
          optionA: "A. at",
          optionB: "B. around",
          optionC: "C. for",
          correctAnswer: "B. around",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Is there something lying outside the door?' which preposition indicates location?",
          optionA: "A. outside",
          optionB: "B. lying",
          optionC: "C. door",
          correctAnswer: "A. outside",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When can a preposition be placed at the end of a sentence?",
          optionA: "A. In declarative sentences",
          optionB: "B. In interrogative sentences",
          optionC: "C. In exclamatory sentences",
          correctAnswer: "B. In interrogative sentences",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of a preposition showing time?",
          optionA: "A. across",
          optionB: "B. within",
          optionC: "C. during",
          correctAnswer: "C. during",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Our school is located behind the post office near the bank,' what prepositions indicate location?",
          optionA: "A. behind, near",
          optionB: "B. located, post",
          optionC: "C. in, on",
          correctAnswer: "A. behind, near",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What type of words are attached with 'for' to form fixed expressions?",
          optionA: "A. Verbs",
          optionB: "B. Nouns",
          optionC: "C. Adjectives",
          correctAnswer: "B. Nouns",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Bananas are sold by the dozen,' which preposition shows measure and rate?",
          optionA: "A. by",
          optionB: "B. for",
          optionC: "C. with",
          correctAnswer: "A. by",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which preposition is used in the sentence 'The rich must not look down upon the poor'?",
          optionA: "A. upon",
          optionB: "B. with",
          optionC: "C. at",
          correctAnswer: "A. upon",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "There are two types of ___________: Simple Prepositions and Compound Prepositions.",
          optionA: "A. Verbs",
          optionB: "B. Adjectives",
          optionC: "C. Prepositions",
          correctAnswer: "C. Prepositions",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Compound Prepositions are formed by joining ___________ words together.",
          optionA: "A. One",
          optionB: "B. Two",
          optionC: "C. Three",
          correctAnswer: "B. Two",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositional Phrases comprise phrases and are also known as ___________.",
          optionA: "A. Complex Prepositions",
          optionB: "B. Clauses",
          optionC: "C. Compound Sentences",
          correctAnswer: "A. Complex Prepositions",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositions are often used for indicating ___________, such as place, time, agency, and manner.",
          optionA: "A. Emotions",
          optionB: "B. Colors",
          optionC: "C. Actions",
          correctAnswer: "A. Emotions",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Generally, a Preposition is placed before its ___________.",
          optionA: "A. Subject",
          optionB: "B. Object",
          optionC: "C. Verb",
          correctAnswer: "B. Object",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositions can be put at the end of a sentence in ___________.",
          optionA: "A. Interrogative sentences",
          optionB: "B. Declarative sentences",
          optionC: "C. Exclamatory sentences",
          correctAnswer: "A. Interrogative sentences",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Prepositions show how people travel, such as ___________.",
          optionA: "A. On, in",
          optionB: "B. By, into",
          optionC: "C. Over, under",
          correctAnswer: "B. By, into",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Words Attached with 'in,' like 'absorbed in' and 'proficient in,' form expressions related to ___________.",
          optionA: "A. Time",
          optionB: "B. Emotions",
          optionC: "C. Skills",
          correctAnswer: "C. Skills",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the modern period, various materials were tried for painting in India, including ___________.",
          optionA: "A. Stone and clay",
          optionB: "B. Canvas, paper, watercolor, and oil color",
          optionC: "C. Wood and earth",
          correctAnswer: "B. Canvas, paper, watercolor, and oil color",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The negative aspect of the synthesis of different forms of art is the ___________ to unique art forms.",
          optionA: "A. Enhancement",
          optionB: "B. Preservation",
          optionC: "C. Threat",
          correctAnswer: "C. Threat",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Simple Prepositions are formed by joining two words together.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Compound Prepositions are made up of a single word.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositional Phrases consist of a single word expressing location.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositions are only used to indicate emotions and feelings.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In declarative sentences, Prepositions can be placed at the end of a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositions can show how people travel, indicating modes such as by, in, on, etc.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Words Attached with 'in' usually form expressions related to time.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Bananas are sold by the dozen,' the preposition 'by' indicates measure and rate.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The synthesis of different forms of art always enhances the uniqueness of each art form.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the modern period, various materials such as stone and clay were tried for painting in India.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
